// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is any evidence of ancient life called?",
    answer: "B. a fossil",
    options: [
      "A. half - life",
      "B. a fossil",
      "C. unconformity",
      "D. disconformity",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following conditions makes fossil formation more likely?",
    answer: "A. buried slowly",
    options: [
      "A. buried slowly",
      "B. attacked by scavengers",
      "C. made of hard parts",
      "D. composed of soft parts",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "To say 'the present is the key to the past' is a way to describe which of the following principles?",
    answer: "D. Uniformitarianism",
    options: [
      "A. Superposition",
      "B. Succession",
      "C. Radioactivity",
      "D. Uniformitarianism",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which process forms new elements?",
    answer: "D. Radioactive decay",
    options: [
      "A. Superposition",
      "B. Permineralization",
      "C. Uniformitarianism",
      "D. Radioactive decay",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In one type of radioactive decay, which of the following breaks down, releasing an electron?",
    answer: "C. beta particle",
    options: [
      "A. Alpha particle",
      "B. proton",
      "C. beta particle",
      "D. neutron",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is referred to as the age compared with the ages of other rocks?",
    answer: "D. Relative Age",
    options: [
      "A. Extrusions",
      "B. Intrusions",
      "C. Absolute Age",
      "D. Relative Age",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What do you call the number of years since the rock formed?",
    answer: "C. Absolute Age",
    options: [
      "A. Extrusions",
      "B. Intrusions",
      "C. Absolute Age",
      "D. Relative Age",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following principles explains how layers of sedimentary rock extend sideways in the same order?",
    answer: "B. Lateral Continuity",
    options: [
      "A. Superposition",
      "B. Lateral Continuity",
      "C. Horizontality",
      "D. Unconformity",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following principles explains how sedimentary rocks are normally laid down in order, one on top of another?",
    answer: "A. Superposition",
    options: [
      "A. Superposition",
      "B. Lateral Continuity",
      "C. Horizontality",
      "D. Unconformity",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following principles explains how sedimentary rocks are laid down in flat (horizontal) layers, although these can later tilt and fold?",
    answer: "C. Horizontality",
    options: [
      "A. Superposition",
      "B. Lateral Continuity",
      "C. Horizontality",
      "D. Unconformity",
    ],
  },
];
